unigauge.com 2019-10-20

# Uni-GAUGE Privacy Policy - Uni-GAUGE-E 2019 Online Entrance Exam for Engineering Courses like Aeronautical Engineering, Civil Engineering, Electrical Engineering and many more streams

The User’s right to privacy is of paramount importance to **Educational Rating and Assessment Foundation (ERA Foundation) and its online brand entity – Unigauge.com**. Any information provided by the User will not be shared with any third party, except for the intended purpose for which such information is provided by the User, in which case User’s consent is implied. Unigauge.com reserves the right to use the information to provide the User a more personalized online experience.

If the Site provides links to websites and access to content, products and services from third parties, including users, advertisers, affiliates and sponsors of the Site, you agree that Unigauge.com is not responsible for the availability of, and content provided on, third-party websites. The User is requested to peruse the policies posted by other websites regarding privacy and other topics before use. Unigauge.com is not responsible for third party content accessible through the Site, including opinions, advice, statements and advertisements, and User shall bear all risks associated with the use of such content. Unigauge.com is not responsible for any loss or damage of any sort which User may incur from dealing with any third party.

In general, you can visit Unigauge.com’s websites without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when Unigauge.com may need information from you.

Unigauge.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide the services as agreed or intended to be generally provided through the Site or any other service you’ve specifically requested, when Unigauge.com has your permission, or under the following circumstances:

Unigauge.com provides the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Unigauge.com under strict confidentiality agreements.

Unigauge.com responds to court orders or legal process, or to establish or exercise its legal rights or defend against legal claims;

Unigauge.com believes it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.

Unigauge.com transfers information about User if Unigauge.com is acquired by or merged with another company.

A user may choose to give Unigauge.com personal information, such as your name and address or e-mail id that may be needed, for example, to correspond with you, or to provide you with a subscription. You may send or upload your personal profile, CV, with all your personal, academic and professional background however you agree that you shall not upload or post any obscene, defamatory annoying material on the website. If you tell us that you do not want us to use this information as a basis for further contact with you, Unigauge.com will respect your decision. Unigauge.com intends to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. Unigauge.com will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. To correct inaccuracies in your personal information please return the message containing the inaccuracies to Unigauge.com with details of the correction requested.

Unigauge.com sometimes collects anonymous information from visits to the Site to help us provide better customer service. For example, Unigauge.com keeps track of the domains from which people visit and Unigauge.com also measures visitor activity on the Site, but Unigauge.com does so in ways that keeps the information anonymous. Unigauge.com or its affiliates or vendors may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service. Unigauge.com maintains the highest levels of confidentiality for this information, our affiliates and vendors follow the same high levels of confidentiality.

This anonymous information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level. If you do not want your details to be used in this manner, you can either disable your cookies or opt-out at the download or request page.
